https://www.rocketarium.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
The "Rocketarium.com" web site is maintained and operated by "Denau Hobby Supplies Ltd.". We are committed to protecting your privacy at all times and in all situations. The information we collect about you is used to process your orders and to provide a more personalized experience on our site. "Denau Hobby Supplies Ltd." guarantees complete security on information stored on our servers. We have a dedicated server for this website, so your information is not stored together with other websites.
If you choose to use PayPal to process the payment - paypal's privacy policy applies. You can read PayPal privacy policy here.
How Do We Use the Information We Collect?
When you place and order, we ask you to fill out a form that requests your name, address and e-mail address.
During the checkout we send billing address and credit card details to credit card processing company. We do not keep or store your credit card details.
Your address information is also made available to the carrier. When required (international shipping) we will also share your telephone number with the carrier.
"Denau Hobby Supplies Ltd." will not share data with any other party.
Your name and address information is used solely to process orders. This information will NEVER be sold, given, rented or traded to others for purposes other than order fulfilment or if required by government regulations.
Back-In-Stock Notifications
If you choose to use our back-in-stock notification service we will ask you for your name and email address. The email you provide is used solely to notify you about the products back in stock and is removed from the system after such notification was sent.
Our Use of Log Files
When you visit our site we automatically log your IP address, your browser type
and your access times. We utilize this information to conduct site performance evaluations,
to see where visitors are coming from and to keep track of click stream data (the
screens our users visit on our site). This data helps us to determine what content
our members find most appealing so that we can maximize your enjoyment of the site.
Correcting/Updating Your Personal Information
You may choose to create an account with us. After creating an account with "rocketarium.com" you may correct/update your personal information by clicking on the 'My Account' link
at the top of any page, entering your ID, password and birth date when prompted
and clicking the Edit Information button. The changes you make will be reflected
in our databases instantly. If you wish to deactivate your account, you may contact
our member services group through the 'My Account' section, or the 'Contact Us'
form.
Links To Other Sites
This Web site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click
on one of these links, you may be leaving the "rocketarium.com" site
and entering another Web site. These sites may independently collect or request
information about you and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of these
linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.
Communication
You will receive communication from us 1) if you contact us for a particular
reason, 2) to receive order updates such as received, shipped, or 3) we need to contact you for administrative purposes. Administrative e-mails will not contain promotional
materials.
At this time we do not send any promotional emails.
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal
information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action
is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal
process served on our Web site.
Supplementation
We may correct or supplement your address information with standardized postal representation
in order to ensure that your orders are delivered. We do this since we want to make
sure that our members receive the order and to lower costs associated with our programs.
Our Use of Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer's hard
drive which identify you when you enter. The ability to select samples on our site
is not cookie-driven. We may use session cookies to provide a seamless experience
on the site and to combine with our log files so that we can understand our site
traffic and analyse our demographic information in aggregate form.
Your Feedback is Always Welcome
We welcome your comments and questions about our privacy policy - or anything else
you might want to talk about. To contact us click
here.
Back
Our Rocket Kits
All Rocket Kits
Bulk Rocket Packs
Trident Series
Cluster
Scale
Sport Flier
Parts & Supplies
Aerotech Motor HardwareCesaroni Motor HardwareAdhesives / GlueAirframes / TubesAltimeters, Timers, GPSBalsa/BasswoodBulkheadsCentering,Thrust & Cluster RingsCluster CablesCluster MountsCouplersDisplay StandsEjection BafflesFinishingAerotech Plastic FinsHeat Shields, WaddingIgnition SuppliesLaunch Lugs & Rail GuidesMisc. HardwareMotor ClipsMotor MountsMotor Retention & AdaptersMotor TubesNose ConesPayload & Altimeter BaysParachutes & StreamersShock Cords, StrapsTools
Bulk Parts
Airframes / TubesParachutes and StreamersCouplersEjection BafflesLaunch LugsMotor MountsNose ConesShock Cords
Store information
About UsShippingOrdering & ReturnsPrivacy PolicyConditions of UseContact UsRetailers
Our Rocket Kits
All Rocket Kits
Bulk Rocket Packs
Trident Series
Cluster
Scale
Sport Flier
Two-Stage
Parts & Supplies
Aerotech Motor HardwareCesaroni Motor HardwareAdhesives / GlueAirframes / TubesAltimeters, Timers, GPSBalsa/BasswoodBulkheadsCentering,Thrust & Cluster RingsCluster CablesCluster MountsCouplersDisplay StandsEjection BafflesFinishingAerotech Plastic FinsHeat Shields, WaddingIgnition SuppliesLaunch Lugs & Rail GuidesMisc. HardwareMotor ClipsMotor MountsMotor Retention & AdaptersMotor TubesNose ConesPayload & Altimeter BaysParachutes & StreamersShock Cords, StrapsTools
Bulk Parts
Airframes / TubesParachutes and StreamersCouplersEjection BafflesLaunch LugsMotor MountsNose ConesShock Cords
Store information
About UsShippingOrdering & ReturnsPrivacy PolicyConditions of UseContact UsRetailers
Copyright © 2020 Denau Hobby Supplies Ltd.
